sigma-global.com 2017-07-11

# Privacy policy | SIGMA GLOBAL VISION

At the SIGMA Corporation of Japan (hereinafter called SIGMA), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We fully appreciate receiving your personal information and will follow the law of privacy in order to protect your information and will treat your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy defined below. 

Personal information referred to in this Privacy Policy means information about an identifiable individual, including name, telephone number, date of birth, e-mail address etc. 

We may request that you provide specific information about yourself and retain this personal information for as long as is necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected. 

When you provide us with personal information, we will use it only in accordance with the purpose for which it was provided. In addition, we will never use your personal information for any other purpose except when you give us permission for using your information. 

SIGMA will never disclose your personal information to third parties without your agreement, with the following exceptions. 

  * • When demanded by law.
  * • For protecting a right and property of consumer, SIGMA or third parties and difficult to obtain agreement from consumers.
  * • When required to cooperate with the person ordered by national authority, local government, or person who are entrusted from such governmental authorities in order to achieve the affairs ordered by laws and receiving agreement from the consumers is obstruction for performance of these affairs.
  * • If the customer cannot be identified by the information, we may use it for statistical purposes.
  * • For providing your personal information to third parties such as partners, sub contractors or affiliates of SIGMA within the limited scope necessary to achieve the accomplishment of our business.

SIGMA makes all reasonable efforts to ensure that customer's individual information is kept current, accurate and secure, thus preventing the leaking, loss, falsification and destruction of your private information. 

Every time you view our Web page, we may store web server logs which show your IP address and domain name. In addition we may store other information which your Web browser passes to us. We will not share any of the information collected in this way with anyone outside this organization. However, access logs can be used for the maintenance of this web site and statistical purposes only.
